NGUYEN TRAN PHUONG DUY

Software Engineer

👑 20/10/2000 | 📞 (+84) 966 740 812 | 🔀 duyntp2000@gmail.com | 😯 howznguyen

1 INTRODUCE

With many years of experience in web programming and has programmed many projects. I want to use these skills to contribute to the company and develop myself. I am a person who is always willing to learn new things and always try to do my best.

EDUCATION

= [2018-2022]

Ho Chi Minh City University of Food Industry (Software Technology)

(**P** GPA: 3.03/4.0)

© CAREER OBJECTIVE

Enhance my knowledge and capabilities by working in a dynamic environment.

Devote to knowledge and strength to the company.

Become a key and important member of the company during working time.

SOFT SKILLS

- Responsibility
- Self-learning
- ▼ Teamwork
- Flexibility
- Problem-solving
- Communication
- Inventive
- Decisive
- Presentation

EXPERIENCE

曲 [12/2016 - 05/2022] ITRUM Forum - Founder

Founded a forum for IT students to share knowledge and experience. Managed and developed the forum.

苗 [04/2020 - Present] MindX Technology School - Programming Lecturer

Assisted in the instruction of lecture for web and game development. Instruct and guide students in using Scratch, GameMaker,

HTML, CSS, JS, Firebase, Python.

苗 [07/2021 - 03/2024] Cube System Vietnam Co., Ltd - Software Engineer

Develop and maintain company projects.

Using PHP, Laravel, Codelgniter, ExpressJS, MySQL, PostgreSQL, HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap to develop system.

苗 [08/2023 - Present] Korecent Solutions Pvt. - Freelancer Developer Develop and maintain company projects.

</> </> SKILLS

</> Layout & Design

5 HTML 를 CSS

Tailwind CSS

B Bootstrap

Programming Languages

Js JavaScript

TS TypeScript

PHP PHP

Python

PROJECTS

MSR [11/2021 - 02/2022]

Description: Website of Banking System **Technologies:** Angular, PostgreSQL, NodeJS **Role:** Front-end Developer, Manual Tester

🖸 Cube System Vietnam - HomePage [03/2022 - 04/2022]

Description: Develop a website of Cube System Vietnam.

Technologies: PHP, WordPress, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

Role: Web Developer

SHIMADA Shoji Warehouse Management System [05/2022 -

10/2022]

Description: Develop a website for users, managers, and administrators to

manage the warehouse.

Technologies: PHP, Codelgniter, PostgreSQL, NodeJS (Socket.io)

Role: Web Developer, Database Designer, Test Automation

SBS [07/2022 - 08/2022]

Description: Develop a website for users, vehicles management

Technologies: ReactJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, PostgreSQL

Role: Backend Developer, Database Designer

☑ ICONIC Survey [11/2022 - 01/2023]

Description: Develop a website for suvery, users, managers, and administrators

to manage the survey.

Technologies: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Docker, AWS

Role: Backend Developer, Frontend Developer, Database Designer, DevOps,

Pull Request Reviewer

CUBECOIN [04/2023- 03/2024]

Description: Maintain and develop the company's Blockchain virtual currency

system.

Technologies: Python, VueJS, Flutter, PostgreSQL, Go-Ethereum, AWS

(Lambda, S3, RDS, EC2, API Gateway)

Role: Backend Developer (Python), Frontend Developer (VueJS)

Framework







Express JS





Database







Environments









Tools



